<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Daniel Dench</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Daniel Dench</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Courses Taught (Queens College): Intro to Macroeconomics, Intermediate Microeconomics
Zicklin School for Online Learning: For the past 3 years I have worked for Ted Joyce to help students in business classes learn excel through an online automatically graded system. The courses span 5 classes with approximate enrollment of 5,000 students a semester. For the past 2 years I have been the senior IT Fellow, responsible for organizing the others graduate students to answer student questions about excel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoderPortfolioの特徴</title>
      <link>/posts/featuresofcoderportfolio.ja/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/featuresofcoderportfolio.ja/</guid>
      <description>変更点 ShortCode &amp;ldquo;private content&amp;rdquo;を追加しました 綺麗なサイトを崩さずに、あなたの個人的なコンテンツ（趣味や感情）を簡単に伝えることができます。
実際の動きについては、&amp;rdquo;テーマデモ&amp;rdquo;をご覧ください。
リンクに赤い下線のアニメーションを追加しました サイトがよりカラフルに美しくなりました。
SNSシェアのボタンを追加しました あなたの記事がより影響力を持つようになりました。
コードのハイライトを変更しました 日本のサービス Qiita のハイライトを参照しました。
とても優しく美しいハイライトです。
ヘッダーに影を追加しました より境界線がはっきりしました。
ShortCode &amp;ldquo;portfolio&amp;rdquo;を追加しました あなたの作品を綺麗に表示できるようになりました。 実際の動きについては、&amp;rdquo;テーマデモ&amp;rdquo;をご覧ください。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features Of CoderPortfolio</title>
      <link>/posts/featuresofcoderportfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/featuresofcoderportfolio/</guid>
      <description>Change Point &amp;ldquo;private content&amp;rdquo; short code added. It is now possible to communicate your personal hobby and your own content.
You can use it easily. Please see &amp;ldquo;theme-demo&amp;rdquo; for details and demo.
An animation of red underline was added to Anchor. The site became a little fun and colorful.
The button of the SNS share was added. It became to have an influence when writing articles more.
Changed the color scheme of code highlight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Demo</title>
      <link>/posts/theme-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/theme-demo/</guid>
      <description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
   Heading Another heading     text text   text text   text text     Block quotes are written like so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>テーマデモ</title>
      <link>/posts/theme-demo.ja/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/theme-demo.ja/</guid>
      <description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
   Heading Another heading     text text   text text   text text     Block quotes are written like so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>/posts/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>このテーマはhugo-coderを元に作成をしています。
一見綺麗なポートフォリをサイトですが、より個人的なことも伝えられるようにしました。
変更点の詳細はブログから、&amp;rdquo;FeaturesOfCoderPortfolio&amp;rdquo;を見てください。
それ以外のDEMOのコンテンツに関してはhugo-coderのものです。
質問や、報告がありましたら、下記からお願いいたします。
 open an issue on GitHub
 ask me on Twitter
  Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
 Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This theme is created based on hugo-coder.
I made it possible to tell yourself more by my change.
Please see &amp;ldquo;FeaturesOfCoderPortfolio&amp;rdquo; in the post about the change. Regarding other demo contents, it is hugo-coder&amp;rsquo;s thing.
Have questions or suggestions? Feel free to open an issue on GitHub or ask me on Twitter.
Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> 連絡をとりたいですか? 質問や報告などの連絡は下記からお願いします。
 open an issue on GitHub
 ask me on Twitter  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Address 5 Hanover Square, Suite 1602, New York, NY 10004 Phone (919)-945-4007 Email ddench@gradcenter.cuny.edu </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Portfolio Demo  Coder Portfolio hugo-coderを元に作成しました。
より自分を伝えられるようにしました。
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description>Selected Peer-Reviewed Publications &amp;dagger;: equal co-authorship 
Income, the earned income tax credit, and infant health revisited.&amp;dagger; Health Economics, Forthcoming Dench, D., Joyce, T., 2019. Does e-cigarette advertising encourage adult smokers to quit?&amp;dagger; Journal of Health Economics, 68, Published Online First. Dave, D., Dench, D., Grossman, M., Kenkel, D., Saffer, H., 2019. Health and the wage rate: cause effect, both, or neither? New evidence on an old question.&amp;dagger; Health and Labor Markets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>